is it Bradley Cooper's dirty underwear
oh oh I did not expect that to happen
I'm gonna be honest he's battled
dinosaurs and even the mighty Thanos and
in his new film onward he's out to
conquer death itself but does Chris
Pratt have a nose to win our game this
is Mel box hi Chris what's up Josh
do you feel prepared for this this seems
a lot more serious and I even
anticipated but I guess let's go back to
your childhood firsts memory wait yeah
go back for me
you okay I'm there you're there okay
back to a little prat mm-hmm what's the
first memory breast milk my mother's
it's terrific mmm okay let's not go back
there what's happened after that just
got gross yeah if someone bottled your
scent yeah there was a Chris Pratt
cologne right were right what would this
smell like what would it be called fist
of farts put that down in onward your
co-star in this Tom Holland yes you
spent a lot of time with Tom thanks to
the Marvel films and this right have you
ever smelled each other's flatulence in
the course of your time together
he's never farted around me but my nose
is so good that I have smelled his
flatulence through his stomach and it's
delightful British people don't like to
fart in front of even themselves they
only fart in their sleep on accident
right that's science do you feel ready
to enter the smell box Chris I'm ready
let's go baby I was born ready now
inside the smell box is Bubba Gump's
shrimpers net catch please get in
position your first challenge
take a whiff what do you know what talk
me through the process what are you
smelling I'm back in Bubba Gump shrimp
company shrimp cocktail
it is indeed the Bubba Gump's shrimpers
net catch that's what that is take a
look take a look oh good I was
impressive that was I did not expect
that to happen I'm gonna be honest now
inside the smell box an air freshener
new car scent the type of like a
potpourri perfumey kind of thing I'm
gonna give you a hint thinking about
Andy Dwyer might refresh your memory no
I don't want actually put it in your
nose but I will if I have to it's really
strong and by the way this is just
completely blown me out for any other
thing that I smell after this because
it's just so strong it's an air purifier
it is an air freshener air freshener
that's like a new car scent new car
scent do you feel the need to cleanse
your powder you okay
yeah and come you got some coffee over
here oh that's great flush it out get
rid of it
you're good perfect
now inside the smell box a piece of
Douglas fir from Nick Offerman's wood
shop
briseida I'm getting some sort of sad
dust getting on the right track I hope
you get this in the nick of time yes
this is something from Nick Offerman
yeah it's wood I'm smelling wood this is
from Nick Offerman's wood shop and this
is a piece of Douglas fir that is going
to be a part of your table no way yes
this is wood from 181 year old fallen
Douglas fir of the San Juan Islands a
piece of history it was born the same
year as Wild Bill Hickok I can't
substantiate that but sure it's true I'm
still with that
Wow you got this from Nick that is so
beautiful now inside the smell box a
raccoon skin hat covered in raccoon musk
oh that is definitely feces oh god it
smells exactly like a pair of shitty
underwear
it's a diaper it's a dirty diaper I
wouldn't do that to you buddy no you
know what to give me him you might have
gone gaga over his directorial debut is
it Bradley Cooper's dirty underwear I'm
connected but not that connected I wish
I had access yeah it's a co-star is it
is it is it oh is it a raccoon pelt it
is very similar to that it is raccoon
scented raccoon hat Oh God
somebody in that hat okay straight
up that is a hat that was worn on an ass
congratulations Chris you are the winner
of the smell box challenge today and
because of that you get to say these are
mortal words please I am Chris Pratt and
I smell great
yes you do smell you later guys
do that is rancid rancid dirty diaper
you